I'm in a hurry to get things done or
what Russian Russians are life's no fun
oh I really gotta do is live and die but
I don't know why that song as I'm
playing through my head for weeks every
time I'm like honoring my piece of
myself that is the opposite like learn
to that lesson learn to the lesson that
life can be slow I can do it at my own
pace because I don't have another option
the issue is is to but that like why do
I feel the need to to okay that like
like if you could be the hair you should
be the hair in that society it's like no
I'm the tortoise and there's nothing
broken about that in fact that whole
story is about starting the tortoise and
how the moving slowly forward gets gets
things done rather than then doing what
you're supposed to do and thinking
you're gonna win the race and then and
they're not getting there and the
tortoise is very much in my mind right
now about like the Trump's the people
who are like hey I'm the star you should
just give me the power and realizing the
the quiet power in the tortoise not that
I'm quiet but the lessons that I have
learned from being in the move from
having to take life on the easy on the
like easy mode on a game thank you I'll
just pick the easy one and the about the
like living life I'm the easy on the
easy setting but society sees me is like
lazy and not able to but it's like yes
but even on the easy setting for me it's
hard like for me that's the hard level
because we all have different Everest
it's like why do I feel the need to show
this but this is my Everest at almost a
pile of clean laundry folded like it
takes two days for my house to be
destroyed and it takes me about a week
and a half to two weeks to clean it up
because I have to be the tortoise like I
have to do things slowly and that was
one of the reasons
I have had been smoking pot during the
day is it forces me it allows me to take
life more slowly because like today it's
a lower day than normal because
yesterday was a higher day of normal
seeing my house cooking the way that
yeah just allowing the process and like
oh the want brain fog today I'm nauseous
and I wouldn't trade today for it like
yesterday like it's today's its new
lesson and new growth and I'm listening
to his coaching this coaching series
called changemakers challenge it's me
it's it's you put like a one-minute
video and you see each other and comment
from this place of love and I figured
out how hard that is for me to love the
person on video is not hard at all to
articulate what I love about them is
very hard to but just love yeah it's
like that's why but one of the things
that was said today which triggered me a
little bit cuz it usually does and then
I'm like no this is the beauty is energy
flows for attention goes and anything
what energy kinda triggers me it's like
every like it's when you're healthy you
have high energy well if you're anyway
you're not healthy then you don't know
high energies I mean you're lacking does
that mean you're because everything else
healthy people try to get that extra
edge in health doesn't work for me so
why would I put all of that time and all
the effort and all of that finance to
not see any results it's like no I'm
just gonna accept where it is what the
general path that works further people
doesn't seem to work for me in a real
way people with the same condition of
chronic fatigue is like everyone's like
exercise its healthy it's like it's the
worst thing to do you're not supposed to
exercise even if all of society and your
doctors and everyone else people with
the condition like that will make you
worse and worse and worse until you
start listening to yourself and
listening to that guide and not the
outside forces you will never get better
better is even a but this energy flows
our attention goes and I'm like oh hey
DeeDee like I don't have attention I
don't have and I don't have energy and
part of means that judgment of like
maybe that's why you don't have energy
because you don't have the attention and
your attention so scattered store energy
so scatter and you have nothing left
like no no because actually my attention
is everywhere because that's exactly
where it's supposed to be to create this
thing in the world so that I could see
like
ATD mind I'm very clear was the thing
that was like yes you can bring in
economics you can bring in science and
we're gonna keep best of capitalism
communism and technology and create this
thing that that is easy to change the
world with it's just about finding your
people and then yes I have low energy
maybe because of that but that's not a
bad thing that's just where I am to get
this thing this is where and it's
exactly who I'm supposed to be I'm
supposed to show the world that it could
be easy and fun to save the world to
start this like monumental movement and
lay the foundation so everyone can live
their dreams and the weird thing is I'm
not going to look at anything like
someone living their dreams to the
outside world I am happy I haven't
achieved health I haven't achieved
financial freedom I haven't achieved any
of that if anything I'm like oh I'm in
poverty and I hope there's no energy to
go around and I am so happy I've never
been happier because I have time to just
sit and feel myself and when you're
living life on on the slow speed you see
things that other people miss internally
and externally and that's what I'm here
to do is to save the world in whatever
way that looks like and to empower
people from where they are that you are
perfect exactly how you are right now
and I love this affirmation that was on
this like kids thing which is like I'm
I'm perfect just the way I am and I'm
growing every day
formation ever and this is going on over
five minutes but that's today's